Privacy Policy of **Xenon Bot**
===============================

This Application collects some Personal Data from its Users.

Personal Data processed for the following purposes and using the following services:
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

* * ### Access to third-party accounts
        
        * ### Discord Account and Discord Bot

    * ### Analytics
        
        * ### Google Analytics (Universal Analytics)
            
            Personal Data: Cookies; Usage Data

    * ### Commercial affiliation
        
        * ### CJ Affiliate by Conversant
            
            Personal Data: Cookies; Usage Data

    * ### Displaying content from external platforms
        
        * ### Google Fonts
            
            Personal Data: Usage Data; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service

    * ### Tag Management
        
        * ### Google Tag Manager
            
            Personal Data: Usage Data

    * ### Traffic optimization and distribution
        
        * ### Cloudflare
            
            Personal Data: Cookies; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service

Information on opting out of interest-based advertising
-------------------------------------------------------

In addition to any opt-out feature provided by any of the services listed in this document, Users may learn more on how to generally opt out of interest-based advertising within the dedicated section of the Cookie Policy.

Further information about the processing of Personal Data
---------------------------------------------------------

* * ### CCPA: Collection of personal information about consumers aged 13 to 16
        
        We collect personal information of consumers between the age of 13 and 16 and won't sell their data unless those consumers have opted-in.

Contact information
-------------------

* * ### Owner and Data Controller
        
        Merlin Fuchs  
        Eduardstr. 10  
        Apartment 1206  
        04229 Leipzig  
        Germany
        
        **Owner contact email:** contact@xenon.bot

Latest update: November 28, 2022

[iubenda](https://www.iubenda.com/en/privacy-and-cookie-policy-generator "iubenda - Privacy Policy generator") hosts this content and only collects [the Personal Data strictly necessary](https://www.iubenda.com/privacy-policy/65675001) for it to be provided.
